hi spring bend in this installment of
嗨，这一期的春季弯
spring tips we're going to look at
我们将要看的春季提示
ooofff
off
in particular how to build an olaf
特别是如何建立一个olaf
server using spring security oauth now
现在使用spring security oauth的服务器
the use case for OAuth maybe might
OAuth的用例可能
allude some people and the reason is
暗示一些人，原因是
because there are so many use cases for
因为有很多用例
it like I feel like a lot of people
就像我感觉很多人一样
probably look into it and think oh
大概调查一下，想想哦
that's not for me that's entirely too
那不是对我来说完全是
complicate or that that doesn't you know
复杂或那你不知道
something different and so what I want
有些不同，所以我想要什么
to do is just ever so briefly sort of
要做的只是这么短暂
lay down some of the youth cases that
列出一些青年案例
motivate the use of and then look at how
激励使用，然后看看如何
to stand up an OAuth authorization
站起来的OAuth授权
service using spring security off today
今天关闭使用Spring Security的服务
we're going to ignore for now the
我们现在将忽略
discussion of how to actually consume
讨论如何实际消费
that OAuth service from the perspective
角度来看该OAuth服务
of a client that I think will be a topic
我认为将成为主题的客户
for another video another time naturally
换个视频自然
will will test that our services works
将测试我们的服务是否有效
as we expect but we're not going to
正如我们期望的那样，但我们不会
build a fun spring based application to
构建一个有趣的基于Spring的应用程序来
consume that a lot of support okay
消耗很多支持就可以了
alright so when people as people are
好吧，当人们像人一样时
building more micro services that
建立更多的微服务
they're building more more systems that
他们正在建立更多的系统
are connected to the open web they're
连接到他们的开放网络
discovering that these these
发现这些
applications these kinds of workloads
应用这些类型的工作负载
are more and more often being consumed
被越来越多地消耗
by any number of different kinds of
由许多不同种类的
clients and this is where a technology
客户，这就是技术
like o of comes into handy for you see
就像的o会派上用场
it is no longer enough for a client or
对于客户来说已经不够了
rather a developer to to think about the
而不是一个开发商去考虑
world in terms of just the user context
仅在用户上下文方面的世界
to the the person that is making the
给做那个的人
request of a service because now you've
服务请求，因为现在您已经
got different clients right now you have
现在有不同的客户
to think about both who is making the
考虑谁在制造
request and on what client that user is
请求以及该用户是哪个客户端
making the request and to give you a
提出要求并给您一个
couple of examples so most of us I'm
几个例子，所以我们大多数人
sure although I confess not me but a lot
可以肯定的是，尽管我不是坦白我
of people use Facebook right and
人使用Facebook权利，
Facebook is a social network on image
Facebook是图像上的社交网络
you can stand your friends and family
你可以忍受你的朋友和家人
loved ones right and the the thing that
亲人的权利和那件事
has become very big for this is this
为此变得很大
sign in the facebook mechanism where you
在您登录的Facebook机制中登录
can find third party websites that allow
可以找到允许
you to click on a button
您单击一个按钮
and then in so doing it redirects you to
然后这样做会将您重定向到
facebook.com prompts you to authorize
facebook.com提示您进行授权
Facebook to - to do whatever it wants to
Facebook要做的事
do right you can spam Mullins and loved
做对了，您可以向Mullins发送垃圾邮件并且被爱
ones and so on on Facebook and then it
等等在Facebook上，然后
and then it redirects back to the third
然后将其重定向回第三个
party website and that when it redirects
派对网站及其重定向
back that started that website website
回到那个网站的开始
now has what it needs to be able to make
现在有它需要做的
requests on your behalf from that third
从第三个代表您的要求
party service right in this place and
派对服务就在这里
this in this example the third party
在这个例子中是第三方
website is a client right the client is
网站是客户权利，客户是
the third party website acting on your
第三方网站对您的行为
behalf
代表
it is a client that is acting on behalf
是代表客户行事的客户
of in my case Josh right it's not Josh
在我的情况下，乔什（Josh）是不是乔什（Josh）
it's not like I'm driving little cats or
并不是说我在开车小猫或
I might be driving the request but the
我可能会提出要求，但
point is they can drive the request now
关键是他们现在可以驱动请求
as well it could be something that's
也可能是
running in the in sort of back-office
在后台运行
mode it could be headless it could be
模式可能是无头的
whatever but they're doing it on my
随便什么，但他们在我身上做
behalf so in this case there's the
代表所以在这种情况下
authorization service which is the
授权服务是
endpoint that we talked to to to get the
我们与之交谈的端点
you get a token into sort of interacting
您会获得令牌进行互动
and get a an authorization code or a
并获得授权码或
token there's the resource server which
令牌中有资源服务器
is the API of the Facebook REST API that
是Facebook REST API的API
contains you know your your friend graph
包含您知道您的朋友图
and your your profile information and
以及您的个人资料信息和
you know whatever else they have in the
你知道他们还有什么
in their API that's a resource that is
在他们的API中，这是一种资源
protected you have to in order to be
保护你必须为了
able to access information on that in
能够访问有关
that iba api you have to have a valid
该IBA API，您必须有一个有效的
token as created by the authorization
授权创建的令牌
service and then finally we have the
服务，然后我们终于有了
client and the client is of course the
客户，客户当然是
third party website acting on behalf of
代表的第三方网站
you the user until you've got these four
您是用户，直到您拥有这四个
things in play and this is you know
游戏中的东西，这是你知道的
common example this is a third party
常见的例子，这是第三方
website facebook doesn't want that third
网站facebook不想要那第三
party website having access to your
派对网站有权访问您的
password and you probably don't want to
密码，您可能不想
access probably don't want a third party
访问可能不需要第三方
website accessing your password either
网站正在访问您的密码
right so there's a little a little bit
对，所以有一点点
of indirection that happens in this
在此发生的间接
particular instance what happens is the
在特定情况下会发生什么
third party website makes a request to
第三方网站向
the to Facebook for an authorization
向Facebook申请授权
code the Facebook then prompts you to
对Facebook进行编码，然后提示您
login if you're not already logged in
如果您尚未登录，请登录
and then it prompts you to confirm the
然后提示您确认
privileges it's asking for upon
所要求的特权
at which point if you if you accept it
如果您接受的话
redirects back with the authorization
使用授权重定向回
code to your third-party client and then
编码到您的第三方客户端，然后
the client uses that authorization code
客户使用该授权码
to get what's called an access token
获得所谓的访问令牌
which then can use to to make subsequent
然后可以用来进行后续
calls to the Facebook API the resource
调用Facebook API资源
that's been protected this is one kind
被保护了，这是一种
of flow it's a very common flow you'll
流，这是很常见的流
see this I think the most often this is
看到这个，我认为最常见的是
a flow that web applications acting on
Web应用程序所作用的流程
behalf of third of the rather
代表三分之一
third-party clients and services and API
第三方客户端和服务以及API
is acting on your behalf
代表你行事
we'll use it's the kind of flow that
我们将使用这种流程
browser applications will use now these
浏览器应用程序现在将使用这些
new browser applications historically
历史上新的浏览器应用程序
there's another flow called the implicit
还有另一种流叫做隐式
grant which skipped the authorization
跳过授权的授予
code or rather sorry had skipped the
代码或相当抱歉跳过了
requirement to send a what's called
要求发送所谓的
client secret and that that made it
客户机密，这就是事实
easier for browsers to get access to a
浏览器更容易访问
token but I think it's you know and that
令牌，但我想是你知道的
can be wrong but as far as I've seen
可能是错误的，但据我所知
it's been sort of superseded by the
它已经被
recommendation that the that most people
建议那个大多数人
use the authorization code flow and and
使用授权码流程和
simply omit a crooked client credential
只需忽略弯曲的客户凭证
secret either a client secret there's
秘密或者是客户秘密
that flow there's another flow called
那个流还有另一个流
the password flow write the password
密码流程写密码
grant and in this case instead of having
授予，在这种情况下，
a third party client make a call on your
第三方客户打电话给您
behalf but by first being redirected to
代表，但首先要重定向到
the trusted authorization service that
受信任的授权服务
you know they the Facebook website where
你知道他们在Facebook网站上
they then promptly login is one in this
然后他们迅速登录就是其中之一
case a client submits or transmits
客户提交或传输的情况
you're using a password on your behalf
您代表您使用密码
directly to the authorization service
直接到授权服务
right so this is a common example in a
对，所以这是一个常见的例子
native application and in particular
本机应用程序，尤其是
this is something that you know that you
这是你知道的东西
would hope would only be done by the
希望只会由
company that builds the API in the first
首先建立API的公司
place so Facebook that app you know the
放置在Facebook上，您知道的应用
the iOS application as developed by the
由开发的iOS应用
folks at Facebook would be something
在Facebook的人会是
that is developed with the with a
与一起开发的
password grant in this case it makes no
在这种情况下，密码授予不会
sense for the native face
对本地面孔的感觉
the application on iOS to redirect you
iOS上的应用程序以重定向您
to facebook.com asking for permission
到facebook.com寻求许可
for Facebook app to access your Facebook
让Facebook应用访问您的Facebook
information on facebook.com right of
在facebook.com上的信息的权利
course they can access your information
他们当然可以访问您的信息
and of course there's no real worry
当然没有真正的担心
about them having or you know
关于他们有或者你知道
transmitting your password since their
自从他们传输密码
Facebook right they already have your
Facebook吧，他们已经有了您的
password and nothing something they're
密码，什么也没有
going to run away and do something
要逃跑做点什么
delicious with your what's your password
用您的密码好吃
if it was a third party website then
如果它是第三方网站，那么
there might be that risk right it might
可能有风险吧
be a third party client that you may not
成为您可能不会的第三方客户
necessarily trust and in this case it's
一定要信任，在这种情况下
very important that you keep your
非常重要的是你要保持你的
password out of their out of their hands
密码失控
because you want that ultimate veto line
因为你想要最终否决权
if so long as they don't have your
如果他们没有你
password you can always log in to the to
您可以随时登录到的密码
Facebook or some other third party
Facebook或其他第三方
website Twitter again or whatever and
网站Twitter再次或其他
say I want to reject this particular
说我想拒绝这个特殊
application because it's performing or
应用程序，因为它正在执行或
behaving maliciously with my information
恶意地利用我的信息
and then you know that's what that's the
然后你知道那就是
those are the two very common ones
那是两个很常见的
password grant and the authorization
密码授予和授权
code grant there's a fourth grant and we
代码授予有第四项授予，我们
talked about the implicit grant there's
谈到了隐式赠款
a fourth grant and that is the client
第四笔拨款，那是客户
credentials granted in this case you
在这种情况下授予您的凭据
know what were the first three flows
知道前三个流程是什么
assume a client and a user context right
假设客户和用户具有上下文权限
it's a client acting on behalf of Josh
是代表乔希（Josh）行事的客户
or or gain or somebody else sides if
或或获得他人的支持，如果
there's a human being in there somewhere
某处有人
with the the client credential grant you
与客户凭证授予您
have this idea of a client without ages
有这个想法的客户没有年龄
of context and in this case it's just
上下文，在这种情况下，
this is a kind of this is the kind of
这是一种
flow that back office services might use
后台服务可能使用的流程
things that have aren't given by human
人类没有给予的东西
beings there's no particular user
没有特定的使用者
context associated with it but you want
与之关联的上下文，但您想要
the benefits of OAuth they want the
他们想要的OAuth的好处
ability the protection that you get by
能够获得的保护
using walk and it's a calling workflow
使用步行，这是一个呼叫工作流程
right in this case it's just a client
在这种情况下，它只是一个客户
that has to authenticate so clients in
必须进行身份验证，以便客户
the OAuth world have usernames and
OAuth世界有用户名和
passwords are that they have client IDs
密码是它们具有客户端ID
and client secrets right this is a an ID
和客户的秘密，这是一个ID
and a password and then users also have
和密码，然后用户也有
usernames and passwords in the OAuth
OAuth中的用户名和密码
world these two things are separate
世界这两件事是分开的
concepts and reason for this as is as a
的概念和原因
XML creative Timbre once famously
XML创意Timbre曾经很有名
described using Xand passwords don't
使用Xand密码描述的内容不
scale not on the open web right
不在开放网络上缩放比例
as we just looked at and just as we just
正如我们刚刚看过的一样
Illustrated there's a lot of different
说明了很多不同
ideas for clients a lot of different
给客户的想法很多
notions of clients depends on where you
客户的观念取决于您在哪里
are what you're doing but if you go to
是你在做什么，但是如果你去
you know if you go to any brand out
你知道你是否去任何品牌
there you can think of they probably
在那里你可能会想到他们
have at least an iPhone application and
至少有一个iPhone应用程序，
Android experience as well and they
以及Android体验，他们
html5 you know browser-based experience
html5，您知道基于浏览器的体验
right so that's at least three different
对，所以至少有三个不同
clients got another days when we could
客户又有一天可以
presumptively assume that they will have
假定他们将
just one experience when HTML desktop
HTML桌面时只有一种体验
browser based experience trying and as
基于浏览器的体验
often as that this is not you know this
通常这不是你知道的
is not all of it it's just the beginning
不是全部，这仅仅是开始
right I mean there's certainly a number
对，我的意思是肯定有一些
of other kinds of experiences that
其他种类的经验
startups these days or Apple you know
这些天或苹果公司
companies are brands are are building so
公司是品牌正在建立，所以
there's iPhone of course there's I pad
当然有iPhone，还有我垫
there's a different tablet devices it
有不同的平板电脑设备
may be in tiny different clients they
可能在微小的不同客户中
may be branches or Forks on existing
可能是现有的分支或分支
clients there are all sorts of other
客户还有各种各样的其他
kinds of plans out there as well cars
各种计划以及汽车
nowadays have SDKs which implies that
如今有SDK意味着
there are male cars that talk to
有男车说话
services and those cars have IP
服务，那些车有IP
addresses there are refrigerators and
地址有冰箱和
microwaves are all connected right with
微波炉都与
the Internet of Things this is entirely
物联网，这完全是
you know real possibility if you go to
你知道真正的可能性，如果你去
Singapore the the roads in Singapore are
新加坡新加坡的道路是
connected to a to a grid
连接到网格
they have sensor data that gets fed into
他们将传感器数据输入
a Greenland that sinter data is used to
烧结数据的格陵兰岛
a to do processing and then do
做一个处理然后做
predictive traffic shaping and analytics
预测流量整形和分析
and in traffic shaping right so in
并在正确的流量调整中
essence the the roads have an IP address
本质上，道路具有IP地址
and they are clients for some sort of
他们是某种形式的客户
service there are human beings on the
服务上有人类
planet walking around with organs that
行星与器官走动
are connected to in it and they have IP
连接到其中，并且它们具有IP
addresses so really you know the sky is
解决，所以您真的知道天空是
a limit these days in terms of what
这些天的限制
qualifies as a client and not all
有资格成为客户而非全部
clients are they are capable of the same
客户是否具有相同的能力
kind of guarantees on top clients should
对顶级客户的担保应
be given the same entitlements and not
被赋予相同的权利而不是
all clients are as secure like so off is
所有客户都是一样安全
a specification it so it's a
一个规范，所以它是一个
authorization delegation specification
授权委托规范
is purpose-built for this sort of
专为此类
jungle-like environment for
丛林般的环境
different kinds of plan and this is a
不同的计划，这是一个
great fit for the world of microservices
非常适合微服务领域
right we want to have we want to be able
对，我们想要拥有，我们想要能够
to you know bring in lots of different
你知道带来很多不同
clients
客户
and we want to be able to talk to them
我们希望能够与他们交谈
and you know welcome them into the
你知道欢迎他们加入
system without having to change every
系统，而不必更改每个
single service for each one of these
为其中每一项提供单一服务
clients so if you have a micro service
客户，如果您有微服务
system you know you're going to secure
您知道要保护的系统
them using spring cloud security and you
他们使用Spring Cloud Security，您
can these services become resource
这些服务可以变成资源吗
services these are resources that spring
服务这些是春天的资源
cloud security can declaratively
云安全可以声明性地
secure for you and we'll talk about that
为您保护，我们将讨论
in a and another installment but the
在另一部分中，但
point is you can tell these different
关键是你可以告诉这些不同
services to reject requests that are
拒绝请求的服务
coming from from some sort of client
来自某种客户
without a valid token but all clients
没有有效令牌但所有客户
can you know through one way one of
你能通过一种方式知道
these different grant types one of these
这些不同的赠款类型之一
different flows they can ultimately
他们最终可能会有不同的流动
obtain a token so that means it's it's
获取令牌，这意味着它是
easy to scale out the clients are able
易于扩展客户能力
to talk to your services without having
与您的服务交谈而无需
to change all of your services so what
改变您所有的服务
we want to do is we want to build a an
我们要做的是建立一个
authorization service today now what I
今天的授权服务我现在
said earlier is worth restating Oh F is
前面说过值得重提哦F是
not a solution unto itself right it's an
不是一种解决方案，而是一种
authorization delegation specification
授权委托规范
and then a that is to say it doesn't
然后就是说它不
handle the question it doesn't provide a
处理它不提供一个问题
solution for the question is this user
问题的解决方案是该用户
who she or he says she or he is right
她或他说谁是对的
it's a it doesn't handle the question
这是一个无法解决问题的问题
you know given a user password is that
您知道给定用户密码的是
correct it instead delegates that
更正它，而是委派
particular check to some other system
对其他系统的特殊检查
and it can really be almost anything
几乎可以是任何东西
under the Sun that's the whole point
在太阳下就是重点
either the author specification talks
要么作者规范谈
very specifically about sam'l for
非常特别地关于sam'l
example and it talks about integration
例子，它谈到了整合
with other technologies so the point is
与其他技术，所以重点是
you need to plug in that mechanism well
您需要很好地插入该机制
of course
当然
spring spring security office built on
春季春季安全办公室
spring security which in turn integrates
弹簧安全性又集成了
with everything in the design it has the
设计中的所有内容
ability to add to that question so we
能够添加到该问题，所以我们
need to first I answer that question
首先我要回答这个问题
which is how does my coop service
我的小屋服务如何
no given a username and password whether
没有提供用户名和密码
that you know user is correct enough
您知道用户足够正确
sign so we need to provide it with some
标志，所以我们需要提供一些
way of internet question and then
网络问题的方式，然后
finally we need to configure the the
最后，我们需要配置
clients and their permissions and and
客户及其权限以及
you know Mary you stood together in our
你知道玛丽，你站在一起
configuration for spring security off
弹簧安全保护配置
itself let's build an authorization
本身，让我们建立一个授权
server here okay I'm going to say off
服务器在这里，我要说一声
service and we'll build the musial you
服务，我们将为您打造音乐
know spring security go up support there
知道那里的春季安全上升支持
I'm going to use spring boots support
我将使用 spring boot 支撑
for building web applications we're
用于构建Web应用程序
going to answer our question in terms
用术语来回答我们的问题
you know they we're gonna answer
你知道他们我们会回答
questions about the users by by pointing
通过指向有关用户的问题
spring security off to a repository to a
春季安全到一个存储库
dau based authentication manager and
基于dau的身份验证管理器和
what I can actually have to do all that
我实际上需要做的所有事情
must to get them working but the point
必须让他们工作，但是重点
is we need a some sort of Dao data
我们需要某种道数据吗
access object that can talk to a
访问对象，可以与
database and then given a username and
数据库，然后给定用户名和
password perform a query and return a
密码执行查询并返回一个
response so we're going to use JPA and
响应，因此我们将使用JPA和
we're going to take h2 rather h2 is just
我们要取h2而不是h2只是
an in-memory embedded sequel database
内存中嵌入式续集数据库
that'll make it easy for us to to
这将使我们更容易
protect so let's hit generate and spin
保护，让我们命中生成并旋转
this up and we'll extract this open okay
这个，我们将解压出来
and open that up as well
并把它打开
all right so we have a we have a few
好吧，我们有一个，我们有几个
things that we need to do we need to
我们需要做的事情
first provide some configuration so I
首先提供一些配置，所以我
want this to I'm going to call this the
想要这个，我将其称为
office service all right and normally in
正常的办公室服务
a sprint cloud sort of architecture you
冲刺云架构
have a config server and you can just
有一个配置服务器，你可以
point this to your your config sir but
将此指向您的配置先生，但
as I don't have that setup here and I
因为我这里没有那个设置
don't really care that go out of my way
真的不在乎我
to do that I'm just going to copy some
为此，我将复制一些
existing values that I have laying
我奠定的现有价值观
around for this configuration okay so
围绕这个配置好吧，所以
we're going to say that we want to allow
我们要说我们想允许
logins to run on the debug level that's
登录以在以下级别的调试级别上运行
convenient we don't read that we want to
方便，我们不阅读我们想要的
run the code on port 91 91 again no
再次在端口91 91上运行代码
particular reason so something I've done
特殊的原因，所以我已经做了
before and it's convention we want to
以前，这是我们想要的惯例
run it under a certain context path so
在某个上下文路径下运行它
we're going to make all requests to the
我们将向所有请求
authorization server start with four
授权服务器以四个开头
slash you AAA whenever anything happens
每当发生任何事情时都向您大减AAA
it has to go for such a way and then the
它必须走这样的路，然后
other standard OAuth endpoints okay and
其他标准的OAuth端点还可以，
that's it that's our that's the sum of
就是我们的总和
that now let's focus on the code here
现在让我们专注于这里的代码
we're going to build a vision server I
我们将建立一个视觉服务器
they say and the authorization server
他们说和授权服务器
it's going to need is going to work in
这将需要工作
terms of a JP so in order to do that I'm
JP的条款，为了做到这一点，我是
going to use Lombok the compile time
将使用Lombok的编译时间
annotation processor that I make a
我做的注释处理器
headline that I neglected to include in
我忽略要包括在内的标题
the application when I generate the code
生成代码时的应用程序
from the spring initializer and what I'm
从Spring初始值设定项和我
going to do is I'm going to build a
我要做的是建立一个
simple entity at JP a entity called an
JP的简单实体称为
accounts off a class account and the
从班级帐户中扣除，
account will have an entity at entity
帐户将在实体处有一个实体
and I'll say a ID at generated value
我会说一个生成值的ID
private long ID and then I'll say that I
私人长ID，然后我会说我
want to have a string field for a
想要一个字符串字段
username another one for a password I
用户名另一个密码我
want to have another one boolean that
想要再有一个布尔值
answers the question is this account
回答问题是这个帐户
active right and as we'll see later this
积极的权利，我们将在以后看到
active active boolean will you know
活跃的布尔值你知道吗
it'll stand in for actually a fair
它实际上代表了公平
number of different questions for
的不同问题数量
different questions relating to whether
有关是否
the account active whether it's valid
有效的帐户是否有效
whether it's been locked out at that and
是否被锁定在那
stuff right so there's my I think that
正确的东西，所以我认为
is the
是个
of what I want to describe here so I'm
我想在这里描述的是
going to use Lombok to make short work
要用龙目岛做些短工
of generating constructors and you know
生成构造函数的过程，您知道
argument constructors and two-string
参数构造函数和两个字符串
method etc right actually
方法等实际上正确
so string is probably not a great idea
所以字符串可能不是一个好主意
here since we've got a password so we'll
在这里，因为我们有密码，所以我们将
leave that as is and then what I want to
保持原样，然后我要
do is I want to be able to manipulate
我要做的就是能够操纵
instances of this account repository so
该帐户存储库的实例，因此
I'll say account repository extend this
我会说帐户存储库对此进行了扩展
JPEG repository and I'm going to say
JPEG存储库，我要说的是
that it's a JPEG repository that many
这是一个很多的JPEG存储库
plates entity the type of account whose
板块实体，其账户类型
primary key is is a tough lock type long
主键是硬锁型长
okay and I need to now persist some
好吧，我现在需要坚持一些
sample usernames and passwords into the
样本用户名和密码进入
database so I'm going to create a a
数据库，所以我要创建一个
command line winner this is a springy
命令行赢家，这是一个弹性
component that will when it starts up in
启动时将使用的组件
Ola log records to the database you know
Ola将记录记录到您知道的数据库中
it'll just write data to the database so
它只会将数据写入数据库，因此
when spring starts up it's going to call
春天来了，它会打电话给
the run method and give us a chance to
运行方法，给我们机会
do any kind of application
做任何形式的应用
initialization which is precisely what
初始化正是
I'm doing here and I'm going to just
我在这里做，我要去
create some hard-coded using the
使用创建一些硬编码
password again this is a in-memory
再次输入密码，这是一个内存
database I'm going to need to recreate
我将需要重新创建数据库
these these records on demand or you
这些记录按需还是你
know on startup but of course if you had
在启动时知道，但是当然如果您有
a durable my sequel of postcards or
我的明信片续集或
Oracle whatever whatever it is you're
甲骨文不管你是什么
you're using then you can just do that
你正在使用，那么你可以做到这一点
obviously you talk to a real database
显然你是在和真实的数据库对话
but this is a simple simple demo so
但这是一个简单的简单演示
let's see when you create a few sample
让我们看看何时创建一些样本
users day long spring and that's me my
用户一天的春天，那是我我的
username and my password that desire
用户名和我想要的密码
cloud I do good dr. Spier P web moved
云我做的好博士。尖顶P网已移动
our which security these are some very
我们哪些安全性非常
boring using even password combinations
使用偶数密码组合很无聊
and I'll say that I want to take each
我会说我想把每个
string and split it so I have a username
字符串并拆分它，所以我有一个用户名
a password
密码
excuse me okay and then I want to visit
请问好，然后我想去
every single one of those that's now
现在的每一个人
getting a raise or free gentleman net
得到加薪或免费绅士网
and that's stream and I have an array I
那是流，我有一个数组
have a scheme of arrays with two with
有两个数组的方案
two elements and then right then for
两个元素，然后对
each tuple I want to say account and
我想说的每个元组帐户
posture at save you account
在保存您的帐户时的姿势
and I want to pass in the well for now I
我现在想通过井
want to create a new constructor that
想要创建一个新的构造函数
only takes the username the password and
仅使用用户名密码
the the active side I don't need the
积极的一面，我不需要
actual primary key and so there's all
实际的主键等等
that there we are let's see what that
我们在那里，让我们看看
looks like
看起来像
okay we're going to say to full zero
好吧，我们要说全零
that's the username to full one is the
那是完整的用户名是
password and final one is is the account
密码，最后一个是帐户
active and for now let's just say that
活跃，现在让我们说
everybody's active now naturally this
现在每个人都很活跃
wouldn't be the case if you were using a
如果您使用的是
database via yeah it could dynamically
通过数据库，它可以动态
change can change dynamically in which
变化可以动态地改变
case all of this is irrelevant and so
如果所有这些都不相关，那么
that's fine now I'm going to write some
很好，现在我要写一些
records today we've got that I think
今天有记录，我认为
we're okay there what we want to do is
我们没关系，我们要做的是
now teach spring security just bring
现在教弹簧安全刚带来
security and add spring security off
安全性并添加春季安全性
about our using password database and
关于我们使用密码数据库和
this is the kind of code that you would
这是您将要使用的那种代码
have written like exactly like this I'm
就像我这样写
not you say you would have probably done
不是你说你可能会做
a better job but you would have written
更好的工作，但你会写
this kind of code this kind of
这类代码
integration is kind of glue code to to
集成是一种胶合代码
make spring security to talk to your
让春季安全与您交谈
identity provider whatever that is you
身份提供商，无论您是谁
know a decade ago it's the same basic
十年前就知道
chore what we need to do is to tell
琐事我们需要做的是告诉
spring security that when it gets a
春季安全保障
request to authenticate for a username
要求验证用户名
day long anyway needs to know what to do
无论如何，整天需要知道该怎么做
right at the heart of spring security is
春季安全的核心是
this concept of a dictation manager and
听写管理器的概念
an authentication manager in spring
春天的认证经理
security is a very simple interface it
安全是一个非常简单的界面
says given an authentication try not
说给定身份验证不要
dedicated you know and in so doing Sethi
专心致志，这样做Sethi
is authenticated boolean on this
经过验证的布尔值
authentication object to truth so set
身份验证对象设置为真
authenticated should be set to true or
authenticated应该设置为true或
false right but you should have a result
错误的权利，但您应该有结果
from that the authentication manager
从那个认证管理器
then returns the ultra authenticated
然后返回超级认证
authentication or throwing one of a
身份验证或抛出一个
series of different exceptions right
一系列不同的例外权利
disabled exception locks except some bad
禁用的异常锁，除了一些错误
credentials exception etc this is a
凭证异常等，这是一个
generic very very sort of abstract
泛型非常抽象
interface that works with anything I
可以与任何我一起使用的界面
really any identity provider under the
实际上，根据
Sun anything you can think of can be
太阳任何你能想到的都可以
made to fit work in terms of this
在此方面适合工作
contract it doesn't care whether they
签约不管他们是否
request for authentication is happening
身份验证请求正在发生
or is being done in terms of user names
或正在根据用户名进行
and passwords or a key being transmitted
和密码或密钥正在传输
in the request body or if it's being
在请求正文中或正在
done in terms of
就...而言
you know token it doesn't care right
你知道令牌并不在乎吗
it's very very sort of generic and you
它非常通用，您
can you can implement it how we like
您可以按照我们的喜好实现它吗
there is a specialization in spring
春天有专业
security to support the particular
支持特定的安全性
special use case of you know entering
您知道进入的特殊用例
the question given a username and
该问题给出了用户名和
password is it's a valid user and that
密码是有效用户，并且
specialization it's called the user
被称为用户的专业化
detail
详情
service so these are detailed services a
服务，所以这些都是详细的服务
Java interface that has a very simple
具有非常简单的Java接口
contract given a username you turn a
给定用户名的合同，您将
type or an implementation a big contract
签订或执行大合同
via type user details which in turn
通过键入用户详细信息
contains collection of granted
包含授予的集合
authorities a granted authority is
权威权威是
really just a string it's just a wrapper
真的只是一个字符串，只是一个包装
around the string and the string could
在字符串周围，字符串可以
be whatever needs to be in your
成为你需要的一切
particular technology right it can be
可能是特定的技术
your notion of roles or scopes or
您的角色或范围的概念，或
permissions or kind of authorities or
权限或权限种类或
whatever I they're they're basically
不管我是什么他们基本上是
entitlements things are allowed you're
权利的事情允许你
allowing the client to do right so we
让客户做对，所以我们
have to enter that we have to be able to
必须输入，我们必须能够
provide that collection we have to
提供我们必须收集的
provide the password for the user and
提供用户密码，并
the user name for the user and we have
用户的用户名，我们拥有
to answer these four questions is the
回答这四个问题是
account expired not locked or locked
帐户过期未锁定或锁定
together is the account not expired are
一起是帐户未过期是
the credentials not expired and is a can
凭据未过期，可以
enable and in our case I'm just going to
启用，就我们而言，我只是要
answer all four of those questions with
回答所有这四个问题
the same answer is it is it active and
相同的答案是它是活跃的
of course we'll say yes right so that
当然，我们会说是的，这样
should all be true so we need to
应该都是真的，所以我们需要
implement that we need to implement our
实现我们需要实现我们的
own user details service there are of
自己的用户详细信息服务有
course make a mistake there's any number
当然有错误，有任何数字
of different implementations out there
不同的实现方式
that will talk to all manner of
这将与所有
different identity providers in the
在不同的身份提供者
backend but for our purposes we're just
后端，但出于我们的目的，我们只是
going to provide it very simple account
将提供非常简单的帐户
user details service ok implements user
用户详细信息服务可以实现用户
details service and we're going to
细节服务，我们将
answer the question we're going to say
回答我们要说的问题
when somebody asks me give it a user
当有人问我给它一个用户时
name whether I have any valid user
命名我是否有任何有效用户
detail we're going to use our new really
细节，我们将真正使用我们的新产品
limited account repository ok so then we
有限帐户存储库好，那么我们
are create a constructor and
创建一个构造函数并
we'll move this up here here we go okay
我们将其移到这里，我们可以
so there we go these are very simple
所以我们去这些很简单
particular service that's actually
实际上是特定的服务
implement so account repository dot we
实施帐户存储库
need a find by username right passing in
需要通过用户名查找正确传递
the username and I want to import this
用户名，我想导入
but I'm going to use an optional not the
但我将使用可选的而不是
default user details I'm as Eric's I
默认用户详细信息，我是Eric的我
want an optional uses its optional
想要一个可选的使用其可选的
actually I want an optional account of
实际上我想要一个可选帐户
you know that I can resolve by by using
你知道我可以通过使用解决
so in the spring data world if I say I
所以在 spring data 世界中，如果我说我
want a return value with an optional it
想要一个可选的返回值
will give me the an optional is either
给我一个可选的是
empty or it contains the record that I'm
空或包含我的记录
searching for in this case so here I'm
在这种情况下寻找，所以我在这里
saying finally one record that has it
最后说一张有它的唱片
that username so I'm going to either
该用户名，所以我要么
find it or 0 but it's not going to be
找到它或0，但不会
hopefully more than one otherwise I'll
希望我不止一个
get an exception and so I'm going to do
得到一个例外，所以我要去做
I'm going to say okay if that's there
我要说的好吗
let's map the account to a
让我们将帐户映射到
implementation of the user details type
用户详细信息类型的实现
a concrete implementation of which is
具体的实现是
called the user type so I say account
叫用户类型，所以我说帐户
dot user name account dot password and
点用户名帐户点密码和
here I need to return in all those four
在这里，我需要归还所有这四个
questions so character I need to answer
问题，所以我需要回答
this questions rather account that is
这个问题宁可说是
active now we have four different ways
现在我们有四种不同的方式
and the finally we need to return the
最后我们需要返回
collection of granted authorities and
授予权威的收集和
I'm just going to use a very convenient
我只是要用一个很方便的
little utility class in spring security
春季安全小实用程序类
called the authority utility I'm going
称为我要使用的授权实用程序
to create a Authority list and you know
创建一个权限列表，您知道
these are just authorities these are
这些只是当局
whatever you want to delete in this case
在这种情况下您想要删除的任何内容
just I'm going to get I'm going to make
只是我要去做
everybody a administrator and a user in
每个管理员和用户
the system and and if I if I do that
系统，如果我这样做的话
great but otherwise I need to throw an
很好，否则我需要扔一个
exception remember the contract here for
例外，请记住此处的合同
spring security is that either you find
春季安全性是您发现
a valid user details or you return or
有效的用户详细信息，或者您返回或
rather you're throwing exceptions you do
而是您在抛出异常
not return null that's not a valid
不返回null无效
choice here so I'm going to say couldn't
选择这里，所以我要说不能
find
找
user name okay
用户名还可以
and either way the we our job is done
无论哪种方式，我们的工作都完成了
our we've done what we can to satisfy
我们已经尽力满足了
that contract and and this is again that
该合同，这又是
they say this is just stock standard
他们说这只是股票标准
sort of spring security the kind of
那种弹簧的安全性
stuff you were written years ago now
你几年前写的东西
this is already pretty good we already
这已经很不错了，我们已经
you know off to the races here but we're
你知道参加这里的比赛，但是我们
still not done right we still need to to
仍然没有做好，我们仍然需要
teach spring security ooofff about what
教Spring Security ooofff了解什么
we've just done we need to also teach
我们刚刚完成，我们还需要教
bring security about the clients that we
为我们带来的客户带来安全
want to that we want to stand up so
想要我们想要站起来
let's create an offer service
让我们创建一个报价服务
configuration extend full server I'm
配置扩展完整服务器我
sorry
抱歉
continue off service
继续服务
configure adapter okay and we need to
配置适配器好了，我们需要
override a few key methods here we don't
在这里不覆盖一些关键方法
need over the constructor that we could
需要我们可以的构造函数
these are all no op that is to say
这些都不是什么意思
they're empty they're just for you to
他们是空的，只为你
have callbacks you don't have to
有你不需要的回调
implement them you don't have to use
实施它们，您不必使用
them but they're convenient in our case
他们，但在我们的情况下很方便
we don't want to configure the security
我们不想配置安全性
per se so we'll leave that as is what we
本身，所以我们将其保留为原样
want to implement is our writers the
想要实施的是我们的作家
clients and the endpoints so this is a
客户和端点，所以这是一个
configuration class and we're going to
配置类，我们将要
tell Springs security off then we want
告诉Springs安全，然后我们要
to create an authorization server so
创建一个授权服务器
there we are and in the and the callback
我们在那里，在和回调中
methods we want to tell in the configure
我们要在配置中告诉的方法
for the authorization server endpoints
用于授权服务器端点
configure where to tell the spring
配置告诉春天的地方
Security Law mechanism how it's supposed
安全法机制的设想
to delegate you know the username and
委派您知道用户名和
password authentication and of course in
密码验证，当然
this case we're just going to delegate
在这种情况下，我们将要委托
it to the existing spring security
到现有的弹簧安全装置
configured authentication manager which
配置的身份验证管理器
is going to be Auto configured for us
将为我们自动配置
and that's already odd you know it's
你知道那已经很奇怪了
going to be available we can reject it
将可用，我们可以拒绝它
so I'm going to do something or say
所以我要去做些什么或说
private final authentication manager
私人最终认证管理员
injecting this I'll create a constructor
注入这个我将创建一个构造函数
and we'll pass that in so this static
我们将其传递给该静态对象
allocation manager everyone right
分配经理人人都对
there's our honor the sum total of our
我们很荣幸
of our authentication manager you know
您知道我们的认证经理
our connection the glue that we had the
我们拥有的胶水
right to connect these two different
连接这两个不同的权利
systems and finally we're left to tell
系统，最后我们要讲
spring security of a lot about the
春季安全性很多
clients that we want to allow so if
我们希望允许的客户，如果
you've ever used the Facebook or KPIs
您曾经使用过Facebook或KPI
and you know there's a you know
你知道有一个你知道
developer that Facebook or developer a
开发者Facebook或开发者
twitter developer at Google usually a
Google的Twitter开发人员通常
portal and wherein you can register
门户网站，您可以在其中注册
arbitrary clients right your this could
任意客户对您的建议
be you know the spring tips android
是你知道春天的提示android
client it could be you know your your
客户可能是你知道你的
embedded
嵌入式的
sign-in with flow for facebook whatever
用Facebook的流程登录
either way you it's up to you to provide
无论哪种方式，您都可以提供
a username or rather a client ID and a
用户名或客户ID和
client secret and to specify the the
客户机密并指定
flow that you want to have supported for
您想要支持的流程
your particular use case and usually
您的特定用例，通常
have some sort of that
有某种
form you fill in the details and they
您填写的表格，他们
get added to the database person
被添加到数据库人员
possibly after somebody on the other
可能在另一个人之后
side has eyeballed it and confirmed that
一边盯着它，并确认
effects read about and request with a
效果了解并要求
valid uh sort of applicable youth case
有效的……适用的青年案例
but in our case we're just going to
但就我们而言，我们只是要
build a hard-coded list of clients in
建立一个硬编码的客户清单
fact for Justin billed to one client but
贾斯汀向一位客户收费的事实，但
again and you know if you're if you're
再一次，你知道你是否
some kind there's no reason you couldn't
某种没有理由你不能
point this to a data source that's using
将此指向正在使用的数据源
the DB schema which spring security
安全的数据库模式
profile provides or you can just provide
个人资料提供，或者您可以提供
your own implementation of the client
您自己的客户实施
details service contract again they
再次详细说明服务合同
plant client detail service contact is
工厂客户详细服务联系方式为
more or less similar to what you're
或多或少类似于您
doing in the user details you're saying
输入您要说的用户详细信息
here given a client ID return a client
这里给定客户ID返回客户
details all right so you can provide you
详细信息，以便您可以为您提供
an implementation of that as well in our
在我们中的实现
case I'm just happy to use the in-memory
如果我很高兴使用内存
version let's say that I want to build
版本说我要建立
an html5 client with a secret called
具有秘密的html5客户端
password and I want to say that I
密码，我想说我
support the password flow I can support
支持我可以支持的密码流程
authorization code and all these other
授权码及所有其他
words like it's a very attic arrange so
像这样的单词是一个非常阁楼安排
I can put multiple values here but I'm
我可以在这里放多个值，但是
just going to do password for now and
现在只要做密码，
I'm going to say that I want the open ID
我要说的是我想要公开ID
scope in this case that means nothing
在这种情况下，范围没有任何意义
but it's a it's a scope that I want to
但这是我想要的范围
see supported when I make the request
提出请求时请参阅支持
okay all right so that's one client and
好吧，那是一个客户，
again there's no reason you couldn't
再次没有理由你不能
build you know image to a five client
建立五个客户的图像
and Android Play and iOS client setup
和Android Play和iOS客户端设置
and then configure them each according
然后根据它们分别配置
to the earth to the use cases for you or
走向您的用例或
your organization's clients or indeed
您组织的客户或实际上
any arbitrary number of clients that you
您的任意数量的客户
want to let build in as well I think
我想也要建立
that should do it if we run this we
如果我们运行这个就应该这样做
should go to make a request I've send a
应该去提出要求，我已经发送了
valid request to the token endpoint and
对令牌端点的有效请求，以及
get as valid access token reflecting
作为有效的访问令牌得到反映
what we've just done so let's let's run
我们刚刚做了什么，让我们开始吧
this code
此代码
okay so the application is up and
好，所以应用程序启动了
running on port 91 and 91 and I'm going
在端口91和91上运行，我要去
to use the postman browser plug-in here
在这里使用邮递员浏览器插件
to simplify the task of requesting about
简化请求的任务
a token so remember what we said it's
一个令牌，所以请记住我们所说的
190 191 it's going to make a request to
190 191将向
91 91 you a ba token so this is the the
91 91您是ba令牌，所以这是
custom context path that we've provided
我们提供的自定义上下文路径
and this is the actual standard iso auth
这是实际的标准iso auth
endpoint that we're going to going to
我们要去的端点
call and when we send the request form
致电以及我们发送请求表格时
and say that we accept application JSON
说我们接受应用程序JSON
I'm going to send a authorization to
我要发送授权给
enter basic authorization header the
输入基本授权标头
authorization that we're sending are the
我们发送的授权是
user name and password in this case are
在这种情况下，用户名和密码为
the client ID and the client code encho
客户ID和客户代码回显
the client secret rather that we're
客户的秘密，而不是我们
sending so H 2 O 5 and password that
发送H 2 O 5和密码
does correspond to this title html5
确实与此标题html5对应
password and we're going to send in the
密码，我们将发送
body several parameters are going to
身体几个参数将
send me the password which is you know
给我发送您知道的密码
the user name the user password via the
用户名通过
username itself might you know my name
用户名本身，您可能知道我的名字
and password the grant type that we're
并输入我们要授予的密码
seeking to use in this case the password
试图在这种情况下使用密码
grant type which is to flow this scope
授予该范围的授权类型
again any arbitrary string the client ID
再次使用任意字符串的客户ID
and the client secret so if we make this
和客户的秘密，所以如果我们这样做
request we should get back and we do by
要求我们应该回来，我们这样做
the way an access token that we could
我们可以使用的访问令牌的方式
then send to any protected service in
然后发送到任何受保护的服务
the body I can send this cat this
我可以送这只猫的尸体
request this token rather using a
请求此令牌，而不是使用
request to look like this curl - H
要求看起来像这个卷发-H
authorization bear paste and some URL
授权熊粘贴和一些URL
comm bar right so that what gives you is
通讯栏正确，这样给您的就是
as long as that service that we're
只要我们提供的服务
calling exact reserve server is
呼叫确切的保留服务器是
configured to - to validate the tokens
配置为-验证令牌
and to talk to our authorization servers
并与我们的授权服务器联系
that won't work so there we go
那行不通，所以我们去了
you can now use that authorization
您现在可以使用该授权
server with any valid or client in the
具有任何有效或客户端的服务器
spring ecosystem
春季生态系统
spring cloud security provides an OAuth
Spring Cloud Security提供OAuth
client and so does first sort of spring
客户，第一种春天也是如此
social right although there is some work
社会权利，尽管有一些工作
being done to converge the client story
正在做以融合客户故事
for both spring cloud security and the
用于spring-cloud-security和
spring social and indeed there's even a
春季社交，实际上甚至还有
fairly fundamental reworking of the
相当基本的返工
OAuth support on the client happening as
客户端上的OAuth支持发生在
spring security OAuth gets moved into
Spring Security OAuth移入
spring security proper so we'll see that
春季安全性适当，我们将看到
this is actually a pretty interesting
这实际上很有趣
space and we'll see that that
空间，我们将看到
functionality is evolving fairly quickly
功能发展相当迅速
to accommodate a lot of new you know
容纳很多新的你知道的
requirements of micro services these
这些对微服务的要求
days now we haven't talked in this
几天来我们都没有在谈论这个
installment about open ID all that much
关于开放ID的所有分期付款
which is a sort of a standard way of of
这是一种标准的
connecting different kinds of
连接不同种类的
applications to the specific endpoints
特定端点的应用程序
required for to sort of work with the
需要与
token to themselves
象征自己
we haven't talked about JWT right in
我们还没有在谈论JWT
this case in this scheme every client
这种情况下，这个方案每个客户
every client will need to talk to the
每个客户都需要与
other editions ever whenever it receives
每当收到其他版本
a token in the request body if your
请求主体中的令牌，如果您的
token is a self-contained that is to say
令牌是自包含的，也就是说
if it has the sort of the signed value
是否具有带符号的值
that you would otherwise get by talking
否则你会说话
to the authorization server in the body
到主体中的授权服务器
of the token itself then they can just
令牌本身，那么他们就可以
be you know unpacked in flight you don't
是不是你知道在飞行中打开包装
need to actually make that extra hop and
需要实际做出额外的跳跃，
call it a visit authorization server and
将其称为访问授权服务器，
you can use OAuth with Java or jetty JWT
您可以将OAuth与Java或jetty JWT结合使用
tokens that's another very distinct
令牌是另一个非常独特的
possibility as well all right with that
可能性还好吧
thank you very much and we'll see you
非常感谢您，我们将再见
next time
下次
you
您